A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Administration, 2010-2013
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Real Property, 2010-2013., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 19-21)
  - Recommendations, 2013 Oct-Nov. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations, 2013 Dec. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Redskins Lease (Science Museum of Virginia, Richmond), 2013. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Southeastern Virginia Training Center (SEVTC) (Chesapeake), 2010. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Southeastern Virginia Training Center (SEVTC) / Oceaneering (Chesapeake), 2013. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Starks purchase (Chesterfield Ave., Petersburg), 2012-2013. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Virginia State Bar - Lease negotiations (Richmond), 2013. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Virginia State Police - Firing Range (Powhatan), 2010. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Western State Hospital (Staunton), 2010. (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Series VII. Special Project Files, 2010-2013., Extent: 11 boxes. (Box 22-32)
  Special Project files, 2010-2013, are housed in 11 boxes and are arranged alphabetically. These records document the Secretary of Administration's involvement with and oversight of projects and studies related to Governor McDonnell's initiatives, as well as other miscellaneous activities of the Secretariat. This series includes correspondence, lists, meeting records (agendas, minutes, etc.), newspaper articles, presentations, press releases, proposals, publications, and reports. Includes files related to Board and Commission appointments, Fort Monroe reuse, Pelham Chapel, Procurement Disparity Study, Supplier Diversity Advisory Board and the Women's Monument Commision, among many others.
  - Boards and Commissions, 2010-2011. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Boards and Commissions - Appointments, 2010. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Boards and Commissions - Appointments, 2011. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Boards and Commissions - Appointments, 2012. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Boards and Commissions - Appointments, 2013. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Boards and Commissions - Art and Architectural Review Board, 2010. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Boards and Commissions - Design-Build/Construction Management Review Board, 2010. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Boards and Commissions - Pleasure of the Governor boards, 2010. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Square Preservation Council, 2010-2013. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - CBRE, 2010. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - CBRE, 2011. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - CBRE, 2012. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - CBRE - ABC facilities management, 2011-2012. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - CBRE - RFPs, 2007-2011. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Disaster Relief Fund, 2011-2012. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Dozier Commercial Park, 2011-2012. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Estate of Eugene Miller, 2013. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Fort Monroe, 2010-2012. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Fort Monroe, 2010 Jan-Mar. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fort Monroe, 2010 May-June. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Fort Monroe - Re-use Plan, 2008. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Bowl Food and Fund Drive, 2012-2013. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - NAACP, 2010-2012. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Pamunkey Tribe, 2009-2010. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Pelham Chapel, 2010-2013. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Pelham Chapel, 2010-2011. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Pelham Chapel, 2010-2011. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Pelham Chapel - Background information, 2010. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Procurement Disparity Study - Presentation, 2010 Aug 17. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Procurement Disparity Study - Presentation, 2011 May 3. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Procurement Disparity Study - Report, 2010 Jan 13. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Procurement Disparity Study - Report, 2010 Mar 1. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Procurement Disparity Study - Report, 2011 July 13. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Procurement System - Correspondence, 2013. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Procurement System - Reports, 2013. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Productivity Investment Fund, 2010-2012. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Productivity Investment Fund - Proposals, 2010-2011. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Public-Private Partnership Advisory Commission, 2010-2012. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Richmond Slavery Project, 2010-2013. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Richmond Slavery Project, 2010-2013. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - State Employee Town Hall, 2010. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Supplier Diversity Advisory Board, 2010-2012. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Supplier Diversity Advisory Board - Interim Report, 2010 Dec. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Supplier Diversity Advisory Board - Meeting, 2010 Aug 17. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Supplier Diversity Advisory Board - Meeting, 2010 Oct 12. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Supplier Diversity Advisory Board - Meeting, 2010 Nov 18. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Supplier Diversity Advisory Board - Meeting, 2010 Dec 22. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Supplier Diversity Advisory Board - Meeting, 2012 Jan 13. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Supplier Diversity / SWaM, 2010. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Supplier Diversity / SWaM, 2011. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Supplier Diversity / SWaM, 2012-2013. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Supplier Diversity / SWaM - Meeting, 2013 May 2. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Supplier Diversity / SWaM - Supplier Diversity at UVA, 2010 June 17. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Supporting East End Entrepreneurship Development Program (SEED), 2011. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Supporting East End Entrepreneurship Development Program (SEED), 2012. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Supporting East End Entrepreneurship Development Program (SEED), 2013. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - VCU Burial Ground, 2010-2011. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Capitol Foundation, 2010-2013. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Executive Institute, 2010-2013. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Executive Institute - Presentations, 2011. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Sesquicentennial of the American Civil War Commission, 2010-2013. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Virginia State Bar, 2009-2011. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Correspondence, 2011. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Correspondence, 2012. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission- Correspondence, 2013. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Minutes, 2011. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Minutes, 2012. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Minutes, 2013 Jan-July. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Minutes, 2013 Sept. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Minutes, 2013 Oct-Dec. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Proposals, undated. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Public Forums, 2011. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Renderings, undated. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 1, 2012. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 3, 2012. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 4, 2012. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 5, 2012. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 6, 2012. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 7, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 8, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 9, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 10, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 11, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 12, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 13, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 14, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 15, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 16, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 17, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 18, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 19, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 20, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 21, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 22, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 23, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 24, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 25, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 26, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 27, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 28, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 29, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 30, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 31, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 32, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Women's Monument Commission / Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission - Submission 33, 2012. (Box 31, Folder 14)